<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<section id="1322">
  <number>0</number>
  <name>Motivating Adult Learners to Persist</name>
  <summary>&lt;p align="center" style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: small; font-weight: normal; line-height: 1.231; font-family: arial,helvetica,sans-serif;"&gt;This course supports teachers' understanding of eleven strategies that motivate adult learners to persist, especially those described in the National Research Council's &lt;em&gt;Improving Adult Literacy Instruction:  Supporting Learning and Motivation&lt;/em&gt;. It also provides teachers with guidance to make focused observations of how these strategies are implemented. Many adult learners face considerable barriers to their academic success and often have many competing responsibilities (family, work, etc.) Only by persisting in school are these learners able to set and meet academic goals and improve their learning outcomes. To help motivate students to continue learning and make progress, adult education instructors need specific knowledge and skills in delivering evidence-based instruction that will support their learners to persist. Beginning teachers can gain competence in these areas by working through a teacher induction program with a mentor. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: arial,helvetica,sans-serif;"&gt;To get started, click on each unit's title below and access its contents and activities, beginning with "Course Overview."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: arial,helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: small;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;For technical support at any time, contact &lt;a title="mail LINCS" href="mailto:support@lincs.ed.gov" target="_blank"&gt;support@lincs.ed.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;</summary>
  <summaryformat>1</summaryformat>
  <sequence></sequence>
  <visible>1</visible>
  <availablefrom>0</availablefrom>
  <availableuntil>0</availableuntil>
  <showavailability>0</showavailability>
  <groupingid>0</groupingid>
</section>